<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chicago City Guide</string>

    <!-- Strings for activity_main.xml -->
    <string name="main_title1">Dine n Drink</string>
    <string name="main_title2">Famous Attractions</string>
    <string name="main_title3">Neighborhoods</string>
    <string name="main_title4">Museums</string>
    <string name="main_title5">Popular Hotels</string>
    <string name="main_title6">Cool AirBnb Rentals</string>
    <string name="main_title7">CONTINUE TO GUIDE</string>

    <!-- Strings for Dining Activity -->
    <string name="dining_title1">Parson\'s Chicken And Fish</string>
    <string name="dining_title2">The Dawson</string>
    <string name="dining_title3">Irazu</string>
    <string name="dining_title4">Boka</string>
    <string name="dining_title5">Portillo\'s</string>
    <string name="dining_title6">Sportsman\'s Club</string>
    <string name="dining_title7">Kaiser Tiger</string>
    <string name="dining_title8">Homestead</string>

    <string name="parsons">The sprawling patio at the Logan Square restaurant is the place to be,
        and there are light-wood picnic tables, striped umbrellas, strings of lights, spindly trees
        and ping-pong tables.</string>
    <string name="dawson">The huge patio, with a bar, tables, greenery and high walls, makes you
        feel like you’re far away from the busy corner next to the Grand Blue Line stop. Order up
        dinner, then stay for cocktails.</string>
    <string name="irazu">Never tried Costa Rican food? This spot is simple, authentic, cheap,
        supercasual, friendly—and all about the outdoor patio. Try the steak-and-beans “pepito”
        sandwich and sweet plantains.</string>
    <string name="boka">The terrace at Boka is nice and secluded, and we really can\'t get enough of
        the food chef Lee Wolen cooks. For an upscale alfresco date, this is the restaurant you
        should head to.</string>
    <string name="portillos">The second location of the hot dog chain in the city serves up the
        same dishes you\'ve come to know and love at Portillo\'s. Stop by for a quick lunch or a
        shake.</string>
    <string name="sportsmans">Sportsman\'s backyard has a fire pit, large tables and a canopy of
        twinkly lights. An in-house herb garden provides the bartenders with fresh
        ingredients.</string>
    <string name="kaiser">The specialty here is the Bacon Bomb, a 5-pound, bacon-covered meatloaf
        made with beef, pork and more bacon. Kaiser Tiger also features beer and sausage on its
        menu.</string>
    <string name="homestead">Given a gorgeous roof deck above their pizzeria, Roots, Greg Mohr and
        Scott Weiner open what they’ve called “a literal farm-to-table restaurant”. The patio seats
        80.</string>

    <!-- Strings for Attractions Activity -->
    <string name="attractions_title1">Millennium Park</string>
    <string name="attractions_title2">The Second City</string>
    <string name="attractions_title3">Wrigley Field</string>
    <string name="attractions_title4">Lincoln Park Zoo</string>
    <string name="attractions_title5">Chicago Riverwalk</string>
    <string name="attractions_title6">Shedd Aquarium</string>
    <string name="attractions_title7">Adler Planetarium</string>
    <string name="attractions_title8">Willis Tower Skydeck</string>
    <string name="attractions_title9">Chicago Cultural Center</string>

    <string name="millennium">This 24.5-acre park might be one of the most popular gathering spots
        in the city, known for its free concerts, famous public art installations and its proximity
        to the Loop.</string>
    <string name="second_city">Even if you know nothing about improv, chances are you\'ve heard of
        Second City. This is the place that put both sketch and improvised comedy on the
        map.</string>
    <string name="wrigley">Even when the Cubs aren\'t playing baseball, there\’s plenty to do at
        this legendary stadium in Wrigleyville. Fans can tour the Friendly Confines and explore the
        Park at Wrigley.</string>
    <string name="lincoln">See some 1,200 animals—from apes to zebras to flamingos—at one of the
        last free zoos in the country. The 35-acre attraction connects visitors with animals from
        all over the world.</string>
    <string name="riverwalk">If you\'re looking for breathtaking views of some of Chicago\'s most
        gorgeous architecture, take a stroll along the Riverwalk, which hugs the main branch of the
        Chicago River.</string>
    <string name="aquarium">Anchoring the aquatic offerings at this Chicago institution are enduring
        favorites such as piranhas, frogs and snakes of the Amazon, rays, turtles and moray eel of
        the Caribbean, and more.</string>
    <string name="planetarium">You\'ll have to travel to the outermost tip of Museum Campus to visit
        the Adler Planetarium, but the journey seems appropriate considering this institution\'s
        focus on out of this world experiences.</string>
    <string name="skydeck">This 1973 landmark occupies two city blocks and stretches 1,454 feet
        high, making it the second tallest building in the U.S. Skydeck views from the 103rd floor
        allow you to see as far as 50 miles out.</string>
    <string name="cultural_center">Made up of 30,000 individual panes of glass, the dome was
        renovated in 2008 to allow the dizzying display to once again be lit with natural
        light.</string>

    <!-- Strings for Neighborhoods Activity -->
    <string name="neighborhoods_title1">Irving Park</string>
    <string name="neighborhoods_title2">Edgewater</string>
    <string name="neighborhoods_title3">Avondale</string>
    <string name="neighborhoods_title4">Midway Area</string>
    <string name="neighborhoods_title5">Roscoe Village</string>

    <string name="irving">Once a railroad depot, Irving Park is still easy to reach by train (if
        you\'re taking the Blue Line) and boasts an array of dive bars and coffee shops that are
        worth searching out.</string>
    <string name="roscoe">While it\'s technically part of the North Center community area, Roscoe 
        Village has an identity that\'s all its own thanks to the vibrant community of local 
        restaurants and shops.</string>
    <string name="edgewater">Situated, as its name suggests, on the shores of Lake Michigan, 
        Edgewater is home to beaches, churches and towering reminders of the neighborhood\'s 
        past.</string>
    <string name="avondale">Avondale is a neighborhood that has historically boasted a large Polish 
        population, which is still represented by the Eastern European restaurants and shops that 
        stretch on Milwaukee Avenue.</string>
    <string name="midway">The neighborhoods surrounding Chicago\'s second-busiest airport are more
        than just flyover territory — they\'re filled with amazing culture, food and more stuff that
        you\'ll definitely want to check out.</string>

    <!-- Strings for AirBnB Fragment -->
    <string name="airbnb_title1">Sunny Stunner</string>
    <string name="airbnb_title2">Instagram IRL</string>
    <string name="airbnb_title3">Hipster Paradise</string>
    <string name="airbnb_title4">Artsy Abode</string>
    <string name="airbnb_title5">Playful Loft</string>

    <string name="sunny">Appropriately dubbed the \"Outdoor Oasis,\" this home\'s 1,000-square-foot
        deck and patio overshadow any of its indoor amenities (and those are pretty spectacular,
        too).</string>
    <string name="instagram">This light-filled minimalistic apartment features polished wood floors,
        indoor plants and all-white decor. The back door opens to a lush yard with a hammock,
        firepit and grill.</string>
    <string name="hipster">This gorgeous home is made for artists looking for a healing hiatus. Make
        the vintage art your muse and detox in the underground in-home sauna at this
        photographer-owned abode.</string>
    <string name="artsy">This century-old Chicago greystone is owned by an artist. Situated in the
        heart of Uptown\'s entertainment district, the space is filled with contemporary art and
        complex interior design.</string>
    <string name="playful">Owned by a local photographer, the apartment sleeps two to eight with a
        lofted bedroom, indoor hammock and two extra beds, plus a few couches.The projector and pool
        table are added perks.</string>

    <!-- Strings for Hotels Activity -->
    <string name="hotels_title1">Chicago Athletic Association</string>
    <string name="hotels_title2">Palmer House Hilton</string>
    <string name="hotels_title3">Virgin Hotels Chicago</string>
    <string name="hotels_title4">The Blackstone</string>
    <string name="hotels_title5">JW Marriott</string>
    <string name="hotels_title6">Hard Rock Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotels_title7">LondonHouse Chicago</string>
    <string name="hotels_title8">The Kimpton Gray Hotel</string>

    <string name="athletic">The gorgeously restored and revamped hotel, opened in 2015, boasts 241
        luxury boutique rooms—throwbacks to the club rooms of athletic associations long
        gone.</string>
    <string name="palmer">The opulent Beaux Arts lobby showcases museum-worthy frescoes and displays
        a mural by 19th-century artist Louis Pierre Rigal.</string>
    <string name="virgin">This is a dream hotel for people into design and technology: with an app
        to control the room temperature, a pour-over coffee setup in each room and a Tesla to give
        free rides to guests.</string>
    <string name="blackstone">It\'s simply one of the most beautiful hotels in the Loop and a
        favorite for bands playing at the nearby Lollapalooza music festival in August.</string>
    <string name="marriott">The lobby of this luxury Loop hotel is a stunner—all black and white
        marble and dramatic, curving staircases. The rooms are just as gorgeous, and the spa, Valeo,
        is a must-visit.</string>
    <string name="hard_rock">With Beatles in the bathrooms and Madonna in the corridors, there\'s
        little doubt about this hotel\'s theme, occupying the beautiful 40-story Carbide and Carbon
        Building.</string>
    <string name="london_house">Sitting on Michigan Avenue and the Chicago River, the historic
        landmark building is now part beautiful hotel and part high-end restaurant, featuring
        Chicago\'s only tri-level rooftop bar.</string>
    <string name="kimpton">In a nod to the surrounding neighborhood\'s legacy as a major national
        financial engine, rooms take a cue from men\'s tailoring, a conceit realized in details like
        wallpaper resembling gray suiting.</string>

    <!-- Strings for Museums Activity -->
    <string name="museums_title1">Art Institute of Chicago</string>
    <string name="museums_title2">The Field Museum</string>
    <string name="museums_title3">Museum of Science and Industry</string>
    <string name="museums_title4">Chicago History Museum</string>

    <string name="art_institute">Guarded by an iconic pair of bronze lions, the Art Institute of
        Chicago houses a permanent collection of more than 300,000 artworks, displayed in a
        complex of galleries and halls.</string>
    <string name="field">Founded to house the biological and anthropological collections
        for the World\'s Columbian Exposition of 1893, this museum is still one of
        Chicago\'s most beloved institutions.</string>
    <string name="science">Interactivity is the name of the game at the Museum of Science and
        Industry, which is spreads throughout a building that was originally built for
        the 1893 World\'s Columbian Exposition.</string>
    <string name="history">Not so long ago this vibrant museum was the stodgy ol\' Chicago
        Historical Society, which let you cull through thousands of archived photographs and
        curio.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- Fragment names -->
    <string name="category_dining">Dine n Drink</string>
    <string name="category_airbnb">Cool AirBnB Rentals</string>
    <string name="category_attractions">Famous Attractions</string>
    <string name="category_museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Popular Hotels</string>
    <string name="category_neighborhoods">Neighborhoods</string>
</resources>
